All right, Max. First of all, welcome to
Pittsburgh. I'm going to try to do all
of Pittsburgh nation a favor before we
get started.
>> Yep.
>> Can you pronounce your last name?
>> My last name is pronounced Ehana. So,
Ihana.
>> Okay. Everyone's going to remember that
now, right? So,
>> let's do it.
>> So, welcome to Pittsburgh. What was last
night like for you when you got selected
by the Steelers?
>> Surreal moment, man. Can't really
explain it, but just different waves of
emotion. Um, you know, everybody was
around me, man, from where it first
started. Jo, ASU, my family, my friends
from high school, you know, just
everybody there, man. Definitely one of
the best moment of my life ever.
>> What was your family's reaction?
>> Oh, you didn't see the TV. They was
jump. That was They was shocked, man. It
was just Everybody was excited.
Everybody's, you know, emotional, man.
Yeah, it was definitely one of the best
moments of my life and be able to share
that with them was definitely meant a
lot for me.
>> What kind of player and person are the
Pittsburgh Steelers getting? Just
introduce yourself to the fans a little
bit. What kind What's your style of
play? What kind of player are you? What
kind of player are fans going to be
watching?
>> Man, y'all getting a player, y'all going
to see a player that's, you know, give
it his all out there, man. Play for the
guy next to him, you know, go to war for
the team, man. Try to bring a lot of
wins to this team. It's going to be a
fun season off the field, man. guy
that's, you know, always treat people
right, respectful. You guys welcome me
here and now I got, you know, pay
forward.
>> So, Hines Ward was one of the on the
coaching staff at Arizona State. Did you
ever talk to him before you were drafted
about the Pittsburgh Steelers?
>> We talked a little bit um like here and
there. He's always shared his like story
moments about being in the NFL, but
seeing how he always carried himself,
man. Just showed me what a Steelers
like.
>> Did you have you talked to him since you
got drafted?
>> Yeah, he called me last night. He called
me last night. We was had we was just
laughing and stuff and I was like, "You
going to let him use your Mansion?" He
was
He's He's amazing, man. Just seeing the
work he's done the receiver room, man.
SK is the limit for him. He's a great
coach, but even a better person off the
field.
>> Omar Khan talked to Hines Ward last
night and he said, Hines told him, "You
are getting with Max, you are getting a
Pittsburgh Steeler, a Pittsburgh Steeler
type of player in person." What does
that mean to you to hear that,
>> man? It means a lot. You know, he's got
to see my growth over the last two years
he's been at ASU, man. So, it's special,
man, cuz he's a still. He know what it
takes. He's done it at the highest
level, at the best level out here. He's
a legend out here. So, he knows what it
takes. And, you know, for him being able
to just speak good about me, but also
like knowing that I put in the work too,
it also felt good to me, too. If you can
give people just share a little bit the
background of your story moving from
Nigeria to California at age 13, what
that was like, what that transition was
like for you.
>> The transition was fun, man. I was
young. Uh we actually moved to Atlanta
first for 6 months. So I was just really
excited like we get to see snow and when
it snowed for the first night, we ran
outside trying to catch it and stuff. It
was actually really crazy. But I was
young, man. But you know, for my parents
making that move, man, it has to be a
lot for them. You know, sacrificing a
lot. they built their whole life back
home to come out here and start friends
for their kids. So now I got to get a
better understanding of it and but I was
young back then. I didn't really think
too much of it but just more excitement
just again I seen a lot of American
movies and that's just just kind of how
my mind was flowing at that point.
>> You grew up playing soccer and you
played a lot of basketball correct?
>> Yeah.
>> So how did you transition into playing
football?
>> See I transitioned to football after
high school. So co happened my senior
year of high school. So I didn't we
didn't really have a season. Um so after
that man I'm playing summer basketball
still you know chasing basketball. So my
AO coach at the time he advised me to
look into football and then it was just
something he put me down with the head
coach at East LA. Sat down and talked to
him and had a vision being offensive
lineman. It was history after that.
>> So Arizona State you began to get more
and more playing time and then you know
you wind up here as a first round
choice. What was that transition like?
Mostly playing right tackle, correct? a
little bit of left tackle. What was that
transition like as you began to get more
and more playing time? Did you fall more
and more in love with football?
>> Man, I ain't going to lie. Like after my
first year at Jo, man, I knew this was
what I wanted to do. It was more like
kind of just saying small goals at time,
just trying to just get better and see
how far I could take this thing, man.
Like God blessed me a lot. You know,
without him, none of this would be
possible.
>> As you progressed, did the confidence
grow? and and did and did some of these
you know we've seen you at some of the
bowls um you know the post you know
playing against other top players around
the country and and it looked like you
were a guy that enjoyed going against
the other top players.
>> No for sure man like like I said the
more I kept getting better and you know
knowing you put in a lot of work man you
get confident so that's all it just
takes is hard work and just you know
perseverance just staying through it
throughout all the hard times going to
be a lot of hard times but just
embracing those moments and just
learning from it. I'll definitely say I
was the biggest stand and just trying to
progress every day.
>> I'm sure it's been a whirlwind, but what
are you most excited about in the days
and weeks to come?
>> Man, I'm excited to be a Steeler, man.
I'll definitely say that piece of it,
man. I've been waiting for this, you
know, kind of been like a waiting game a
little bit this whole 3 4 month process,
man. But excitement, I'm excited to be a
Steeler. I'm ready to get to work.
>> Max, thank you very much. Appreciate it.
Welcome to Pittsburgh. Yes,
>> sir. Appreciate too.